[Music]
I'll be honest with you I don't want to
keep talking about these incidents but
they keep
happening I mean if I had my way this
show would just be Larry wmer talks
about his favorite Battle Star Galactica
episodes for a half hour every night
that's
it that's it if you could if you would
uh pull up a map on the screen I could
show you exactly he's got a weapon he's
got a weapon I'm going to need backup
you have a weapon way I got a barrel
roll
yeah wow people are having weddings that
they're holding at like Southern
plantations okay yes you know the ones
that use slaves to run their household
and work on their Farms okay so here's a
few pictures there's one that's very
nice yeah oh nice oh one more oh very
nice so if you're going to get married
at a plantation then your wedding has to
end like the last scene in D Jango and
then you know oh my God I right
yeah hey America Larry Wilmore here if
you like the nightly show on Comedy
Central like us on Facebook too just
don't poke me I do not like being poked
you can Candy Crush me